{"questions":[{"difficulty":"2","question":"Why is requirements traceability important in software development?","answers":["It enables tracking of requirements throughout the development process","It determines the project's return on investment","It ensures that requirements are not changed","t helps in creating user stories"],"correct_ans":"1"},{"difficulty":"2","question":"In Agile development, what is the primary responsibility of a Scrum Master?","answers":["Writing code and developing features","Managing the project budget","Ensuring the team follows Agile principles and practices","Creating user stories and acceptance criteria"],"correct_ans":"3"},{"difficulty":"2","question":"What is the purpose of a Burndown Chart in Agile development?","answers":["To measure the project's return on investment","To track the team's progress in completing tasks over time","To visualize the team's skill levels","To display the hierarchy of user stories"],"correct_ans":"2"},{"difficulty":"2","question":"what does software architecture include?","answers":["Only the structural aspects of a system","Only the behavioral aspects of a system","The interactions between a system and its environment","The fundamental organization, components, and design principles of a system"],"correct_ans":"4"},{"difficulty":"2","question":"What is the primary purpose of program testing?","answers":["To execute a program with real-world data","To identify as many requirements as possible","To discover defects before the program is put into use","To verify the software's non-functional attributes"],"correct_ans":"3"},{"difficulty":"2","question":"What is the primary focus of software maintenance?","answers":["Modifying a program after it has been put into use","Developing new software from scratch","Creating different versions of custom software","Developing generic software products"],"correct_ans":"1"},{"difficulty":"2","question":"In adaptive and perfective maintenance, what does the maintenance programmer need to be an expert in?","answers":["implementation and integration","New programming languages","testing and documentation","Requirements,Specifications,Design,and Implementation and integration"],"correct_ans":"4"},{"difficulty":"2","question":"When designing a survey in software engineering, what is a crucial consideration?","answers":["Using complex technical language","Focusing on positive feedback","Excluding open-ended questions","The length of the survey"],"correct_ans":"4"},{"difficulty":"3","question":"What is the purpose of using architectural patterns in software development?","answers":["To document the project budget","To estimate the return on investment","To provide reusable solutions to commonly occurring problems","To assign tasks to team members"],"correct_ans":"3"},{"difficulty":"3","question":"What is the primary purpose of conductive surveys in software engineering?","answers":["To gather user feedback on software performance","To collect data on specific software-related topics","To promote new software releases","To identify and fix bugs in the software"],"correct_ans":"2"},{"difficulty":"3","question":"What is the purpose of using architectural patterns in software development?","answers":["To document the project budget\t\t\t","To estimate the return on investment ","To provide reusable solutions to commonly occurring problems ","To assign taks to team members"],"correct_ans":"3"},{"difficulty":"3","question":"aaa","answers":["a","b","c","d"],"correct_ans":"1"},{"difficulty":"1","question":"Why is scalability an important consideration in software architecture?","answers":["It determines the project timeline","It ensures that the software has a visually appealing design","It focuses on the security aspects of the software","It addresses the system's ability to handle growth in users"],"correct_ans":"4"},{"difficulty":"1","question":"What is the main distinction between validation testing and defect testing?","answers":["The use of artificial data in validation testing","The intentional obscurity of test cases in defect testing","The focus on system crashes in defect testing","The expectation of correct performance in validation testing"],"correct_ans":"4"},{"difficulty":"1","question":"fgbtfxgn","answers":["rg","nrgtsfn","rsgf","n"],"correct_ans":"1"},{"difficulty":"1","question":"aaa","answers":["a","b","c","d"],"correct_ans":"1"}]}